https://thedivinecomedy.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
This policy explains what data we will collect about you when you use our website and what we will use it for.
Welcome to the section of our magnificent web-empire that explains what we do with the data that we collect about you.
When you browse our website at www.thedivinecomedy.com and enjoy reading all the divine news that we type up for you, we may gather personal information such as your name and any contact details that you give us. The way that you use our website can also tell us your preferences and interests. Hopefully The Divine Comedy is your main interest so we have that in common. All this is data and you can give it us in a few ways..
a. Signing up for a mailing list will give us information like your name and email address.If you enter any details on the website, then we’ll have that too.
b. To improve your experience of using the website, we use cookies. Yum!
Our internet chefs have chosen the cookies that appear on the website very carefully to ensure that your privacy is respected and protected at all times. These cookies are used in accordance with the current UK & EU Cookie Law.
Let me introduce you to the types of cookies that we use on the Website:
1. Analytical/Performance cookies – these let us recognise and count the numbers of visitors to the website. We can also see how people navigate around the website which helps us make the experience better.
2. Functionality cookies – Like an old friend we want to say Hello. These cookies will recognise you when you return to our website. By doing this we can personalise our content for you and remember your preferences.
3. Targeting cookies – These help us by recording your visit to thedivinecomedy.com
They’ll record your visit, the pages you visit and any links that you follow. We use this information to tailor any advertising displayed on here more relevant to your interests. But before we place any cookies on your computer, a pop up will appear to ask for your consent. You don’t have to agree to the cookies, but if you decline then some features of the website might not function fully or as intended.
4. Cookies aren’t for everyone so you can restrict your browser’s use of them – just go to the ‘help’ menu on your internet browser – and if you would like to delete cookies you can do so at any time.
However, deleting cookies from our website can lose information that helps you access this site faster and more efficiently, like your personalisation settings.
5. You can also exercise your control on sites like Facebook and Google where you can see which third parties may be able to target marketing at you while you use their platforms. If you want to stop those organisations from being able to direct their marketing to you while you use their sites then go to facebook.com/ads/preferences and www.google.com/ads/preferences and change your settings.
Now we have you data, what can we do with it?
We will keep your data when you sign up to our mailing list as you’ve asked to be kept informed of all things Divine Comedy related, but we will delete it if you ask us to.
What we use your data for.
a. to improve our products / services and make our website the best we can.
b. Based on the information we have about you, we can send you promotional materials like gig details or products that may be of interest to you.
c. We can use it to contact you for market research purposes dependent on the contact information you have given us. We may then use what we have learned from that market research to customise or update our website.
d. Unless we have to by law, then we will not give your data to any third parties unless they are associated to us like our record company or concert promoter. This is so they can inform you about things that you have told us that you want to hear about.
e. We have a great webteam and sometimes we need people to help us update and keep our website in working order. These could be our wizard web designers or our team of I.T. marvels. They may have access to your data but only so they can do aid us in keeping the website safe and working.
We will not let them use your data for anything elseand make sure that it is lawfully carried out in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998. This protects you and makes sure that your data can’t be misused and must be protected.
We take security very seriously and will do all we can to prevent breaches in our security to stop third party access to your data that could then be misued. We have defined managerial processes for how we use your data and will put in place the needed electronic and physical security to make sure everything is as safe as possible. However, we need to emphasise that any transmission of information over the internet is not 100% secure and that you ultimately send us your data at your own risk.
The internet is not a lonely place and we can link to other websites. If these websites are not owned by us, then we do not have any control on how they handle your data when you visit them.
Always check their privacy policy so you can be happy in how they hold and use your data.
Sometimes your data might travel outside of the European Economic Area (EEA). This could happen if our servers or one of our service providers is located in a country outside of the EEA.
If we transfer data like this, then we will aim to ensure your privacy rights continue to be protected. Within our privacy policy you expressly agress to such transfers of data.
b. If we transfer Data outside the EEA in this way, we will take steps with the aim of ensuring that your privacy rights continue to be protected as outlined in this privacy policy. You expressly agree to such transfers of Data.
Sometimes we many need to change the terms of our privacy policy. If this happens we will let you know and ask if you still agree to use our website under the new policy. We will either post the new terms on the website so you can see them when you next visit or email you directly to let you know of the changes.
Thank you for reading this far. We are nearly at the end, but now we have to look at other legal things..
The privacy policy is for YOU. You can’t transfer your rights under this privacy policy to anyone else. If you have an issue with how the website operates or manages your data and think we have breached them, then you are the only one who can complain.
So we can make your visit to thedivinecomedy.com better and send you the information that you have told us that you’d like to receive, we might transfer our rights under this privacy policy but where we believe your rights won’t be affected.
How to get in touch with the website team:
We like your data and we love protecting it! So if at any time you’d like to see what data that we have about you, please ask us and we’ll send you a copy of any of your data that we hold. Please feel free to email us at the address below for this or any other enquiries that you might have:dpo@thedivinecomedy.co.uk
If you have read this far, then we’re impressed! We hope we’ve made this interesting and that it has been presented as clear as possible. Now go and treat yourself to a chocolate cookie!
The Divine Comedy Webteam.
Live
Music
Videos
News
Press
About
Shop
Preorder
Necessary (Required)
Like an old friend we want to say Hello. These cookies will recognise you when you return to our website. By doing this we can personalise our content for you and remember your preferences.
Name: CraftSessionId
Description: Craft relies on PHP sessions to maintain sessions across web requests. That is done via the PHP session cookie. Craft names that cookie “CraftSessionId” by default, but it can be renamed via the phpSessionId config setting. This cookie will expire as soon as the session expires.
Provider: this site
Expiry: Session
Name: *_identity
Description: When you log into the Control Panel, you will get an authentication cookie used to maintain your authenticated state. The cookie name is prefixed with a long, randomly generated string, followed by _identity. The cookie only stores information necessary to maintain a secure, authenticated session and will only exist for as long as the user is authenticated in Craft.
Provider: this site
Expiry: Persistent
Name: *_username
Description: If you check the "Keep me logged in" option during login, this cookie is used to remember the username for your next authentication.
Provider: this site
Expiry: Persistent
Name: CRAFT_CSRF_TOKEN
Description: Protects us and you as a user against Cross-Site Request Forgery attacks.
Provider: this site
Expiry: Session
Statistics
These let us recognise and count the numbers of visitors to the website. We can also see how people navigate around the website which helps us make the experience better.
Name: collect
Description: Used to send data to Google Analytics about the visitor's device and behavior. Tracks the visitor across devices and marketing channels.
Provider: google-analytics.com
Expiry: Session
Name: _ga
Description: Registers a unique ID that is used to generate statistical data on how the visitor uses the website.
Provider: thedivinecomedy.com
Expiry: 2 years
Name: _gat
Description: Used by Google Analytics to throttle request rate
Provider: thedivinecomedy.com
Expiry: 1 day
Name: _gid
Description: Registers a unique ID that is used to generate statistical data on how the visitor uses the website.
Provider: thedivinecomedy.com
Expiry: 1 day
Marketing
These help us by recording your visit to thedivinecomedy.com They’ll record your visit, the pages you visit and any links that you follow. We use this information to tailor any advertising displayed on here more relevant to your interests
Name: IDE
Description: Used by Google DoubleClick to register and report the website user's actions after viewing or clicking one of the advertiser's ads with the purpose of measuring the efficacy of an ad and to present targeted ads to the user.
Provider: doubleclick.net
Expiry: 1 year
Name: test_cookie
Description: Used to check if the user's browser supports cookies.
Provider: doubleclick.net
Expiry: 1 day
Name: GPS
Description: Registers a unique ID on mobile devices to enable tracking based on geographical GPS location.
Provider: youtube.com
Expiry: 1 day
Name: PREF
Description: Registers a unique ID that is used by Google to keep statistics of how the visitor uses YouTube videos across different websites.
Provider: youtube.com
Expiry: 8 months
Name: VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE
Description: Tries to estimate the users' bandwidth on pages with integrated YouTube videos.
Provider: youtube.com
Expiry: 179 days
Name: YSC
Description: Registers a unique ID to keep statistics of what videos from YouTube the user has seen.
Provider: youtube.com
Expiry: Session
Name: yt-remote-cast-installed
Description: Stores the user's video player preferences using embedded YouTube video
Provider: youtube.com
Expiry: Session
Name: yt-remote-connected-devices
Description: Stores the user's video player preferences using embedded YouTube video
Provider: youtube.com
Expiry: Persistent
Name: yt-remote-device-id
Description: Stores the user's video player preferences using embedded YouTube video
Provider: youtube.com
Expiry: Persistent
Name: yt-remote-fast-check-period
Description: Stores the user's video player preferences using embedded YouTube video
Provider: youtube.com
Expiry: Session
Name: yt-remote-session-app
Description: Stores the user's video player preferences using embedded YouTube video
Provider: youtube.com
Expiry: Session
Name: yt-remote-session-name
Description: Stores the user's video player preferences using embedded YouTube video
